{
    "id": "e3d412d68fb6446aaa0230a2b7ece869",
    "title": "Fill In The Blanks | General Grammar Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "26d5453624a34a248fe2a4fd9543224a",
            "title": "Fill In The Blanks | General Grammar Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Tell me if you ……………………….. any help.",
                    "description": "The simple present is used in situations like these. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "need",
                        "will need",
                        "would need"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The first time I ………………………… him was at university.",
                    "description": "The simple past is used to say when something happened. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "met",
                        "had met",
                        "have met"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "This is the garage ……………………….. they used to work.",
                    "description": "Where means in which.",
                    "answers": [
                        "where",
                        "which",
                        "that"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I ……………………………. a terrible experience yesterday.",
                    "description": "Had is the past simple form of have. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "had",
                        "have",
                        "have had",
                        "had had"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "That is my biggest regret …………………………",
                    "description": "Yet shows time up to now. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "yet",
                        "still",
                        "already"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The valley ………………………….. quiet and beautiful in the morning.",
                    "description": "Lay is the past simple form of lie. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "lay",
                        "lays",
                        "laid"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Each of us ……………………………. the world differently.",
                    "description": "Use a singular verb after each.",
                    "answers": [
                        "sees",
                        "see",
                        "seen"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………………… his illness, he could not write the exam.",
                    "description": "Owing to and due to both mean because of.",
                    "answers": [
                        "Owing to",
                        "Due to",
                        "Either could be used here"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The summer term ………………………… on April 12th.",
                    "description": "The simple present is more appropriate here. It is used to talk about predetermined actions that are part of a time table. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "will start",
                        "is starting",
                        "starts"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "I will pay you back when I ………………………… a job.",
                    "description": "When both clauses refer to the future, a simple present is used after when.",
                    "answers": [
                        "will get",
                        "get",
                        "would get"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I promise I …………………………… in the evening.",
                    "description": "Simple future is used to express this idea. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "come",
                        "will come",
                        "would come"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "I stayed in bed all day ……………………………. going to work.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "instead",
                        "instead of",
                        "without"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}